<resources>
    <string name="app_name">poker_money_divider</string>
    <string name="pair_combination">Pair</string>
    <string name="pair_combination_description">One pair, or simply a pair, is a hand that contains two cards of one rank and three cards of three other ranks (the kickers), such as 4♥ 4♠ K♠ 10. ♦ 5♠ ("one pair, fours" or a "pair of fours"). It ranks below two pair and above high card.</string>
    <string name="two_pairs_combination">Two pairs</string>
    <string name="two_pairs_combination_description">A Two Pair is a five-card combination that includes two pairs. In other words, it has two cards of one rank, two cards of another rank, and a fifth card of a different rank than the first two</string>
    <string name="set_combination">Three of a kind(Set/Trips)</string>
    <string name="set_combination_description">Also known as trips or a set, is a hand that contains three cards of one rank and two cards of two other ranks (the kickers), such as 2♦ 2♠ 2♣ K♠ 6♥ ("three of a kind, twos" or "trip twos" or a "set of twos"). It ranks below a straight and above two pair</string>
    <string name="straight_combination">Straight</string>
    <string name="straight_combination_description">A straight is a hand that contains five cards of sequential rank, not all of the same suit, such as 7♣ 6♠ 5♠ 4♥ 3♥ (a "seven-high straight"). It ranks below a flush and above three of a kind.[6] Under high rules, an ace can rank either high (as in A♦ K♣ Q♣ J♦ 10♠, an ace-high straight) or low (as in 5♣ 4♦ 3♥ 2♥ A♠, a five-high straight)</string>
    <string name="flush_combination">Flush</string>
    <string name="flush_combination_description">A flush is a hand that contains five cards all of the same suit, not all of sequential rank, such as K♣ 10♣ 7♣ 6♣ 4♣ (a "king-high flush" or a "king-ten-high flush"). It ranks below a full house and above a straight. Under ace-to-five low rules, flushes are not possible</string>
    <string name="fullhouse_combination">Full house</string>
    <string name="fullhouse_combination_description">A full house, also known as a full boat or a tight or a boat (and originally called a full hand), is a hand that contains three cards of one rank and two cards of another rank, such as 3♣ 3♠ 3♦ 6♣ 6♥ (a "full house, threes over sixes" or "threes full of sixes" or "threes full").It ranks below four of a kind and above a flush.</string>
    <string name="quads_combination">Four of a kind(Quads)</string>
    <string name="quads_combination_description">Also known as quads, is a hand that contains four cards of one rank and one card of another rank (the kicker), such as 9♣ 9♠ 9♦ 9♥ J♥ ("four of a kind, nines"). It ranks below a straight flush and above a full house.</string>


</resources>
